{
    "id": "d1f2151f3d414e5fa0d6a470beee63e7",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I want you to help …………………………… with my homework.",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object should be in its object form. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ae455e2129bb482199e0fa5e149f706a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she couldn’t do anything to help …………………………..",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object should be in its object form. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "his",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "762ffc0a3d4547b9bd923d169e81b244"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are all waiting for …………………………….",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object of a preposition should be in the object form. The subject and object form of you are the same - you.",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "93df7f5848f44721927d0b55d2d51e23"
        },
        {
            "question": "That cat of …………………………… has scratched me again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "you",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9d37c866789844128374372fbe938184"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a friend of ……………………………..",
            "description": "The possessive form is used after the preposition in this structure. ",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4a1ffd77d31d41d8b240cb830baf24a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of …………………………….. friends is a sailor.",
            "description": "The possessive form of the pronoun can be used as an adjective to modify nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "his",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "791356152c2448dab92a732cb0d17333"
        },
        {
            "question": "None of ………………………………. can do anything about it.",
            "description": "The object of a preposition should be in its object form.",
            "answers": [
                "we",
                "us",
                "ours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f23c03c9fb9b45118f7c91d7d89ca080"
        },
        {
            "question": "Between you and ………………………………. I don’t trust him.",
            "description": "The object is a preposition should be in its form. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5458333cdce476cb9d146649b4e3e13"
        },
        {
            "question": "My car is faster than …………………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aa25e39a2cac41cf895abf5adcb24846"
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns more than ……………………………… do.",
            "description": "The subject pronoun is used before a verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07feb232ec5643a0b0f7ba5a7060cae8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………… decorated the hall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "myself",
                "myselves"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "256c4cea16ed470597701d853d3dbb59"
        },
        {
            "question": "She blamed …………………………….. for the mistake.",
            "description": "Either herself or him can be used here with different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "herself",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9cede5330aad4b36871f715f7181d018"
        }
    ]
}